<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Stifter</title>
    <link>https://samstifter.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Stifter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 09:13:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://samstifter.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RatePoint</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/projects/ratepoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 09:13:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/projects/ratepoint/</guid>
      <description>In this project, our goal was to create a point of interest rating system. Users would be able to add POIs, rate POIs, create lists of POIs and there would be a basic exploration mechanism. We used Model View Controller design pattern in this project separate the data layers from the transport layers from the views. We also utilized a client-server approach where the frontend website got its data from a backend database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HelpTrain</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/projects/helptrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/projects/helptrain/</guid>
      <description>This project was designed to be a tool for TAs to help manage a help queue for when students have questions during office hours or lab sections. In this project, we used a backend server to manage the lists and a frontend view to just display the data. The backend server was written in Express (JavaScript). The frontend was written in React. This was a project for HackISU, so the first iteration was a little rough around the edges, but it got smoothed out a bit later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punch Clock</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/projects/punch-clock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/projects/punch-clock/</guid>
      <description>Our project was an application designed for users who want a way to more easily keep track of how much time they work on their computer. The program is a timer that can either be manually turned on and off or it can be set up to automatically detect when a selected program is opened and keep track of time until it is closed. The overall component diagram of the project is included below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am a Software Engineering student at Iowa State University. I am in my third year and expect to graduate in May 2020. I am currently in my third semester as a Teaching Assistant in the Electrical and Computer Engineering Department for CPR E 288 Embedded Systems: Introduction.
A selection of courses I have taken include: data structures, digital logic, software construction, user interfaces, databases, and computer organization. A full list with course codes can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/contact-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/contact-me/</guid>
      <description>To get in touch with me, fill out the form below and I will follow up with you by email. You can also visit the social links on my homepage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISU Course List</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/course-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/course-list/</guid>
      <description>I am currently enrolled in the courses listed in bold.
 COM S 228: Data structures COM S 252: Linux Operating System Essentials COM S 309: Software Development Practices COM S 311: Introduction to the Design and Analysis of Algorithms COM S 319: Software Construction and User interfaces COM S 363: Introduction to Database Management Systems CPR E 281: Digital Logic CPR E 288: Embedded Systems I: Introduction CPR E 308: Operating Systems: Principles and Practice CPR E 310: Theoretical Foundations of Computer Engineering CPR E 381: Computer Organization and Assembly Level Programming CPR E 388: Embedded Systems II: Mobile Platforms (Android) DS 201: Introduction to Data Science S E 329: Software Project Management S E 339: Software Architecture and Design S E 417: Software Testing S E 491: Senior Design Project I and Professionalism S E 494: Software Engineering Portfolio Development  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://samstifter.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samstifter.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>If the resume is not displaying correctly, click here</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>